You
I don't know.
Let's go.
Impossible.
As simple as that.
To happen so easily.
I suppose most of our lives
End pretty much that way.
Not even saying bye.
Just up and drop dead like that.
Damn, lives you feeling kind of lonely?
Don't it.
You bastard.
What did you just say?
Say that again!
Well, looks like little crybaby
Polnareff is trying to talk tough now.
Polnareff!
Don't let him provoke you!
Don't you understand?
Didn't Avdolsan warn you about
the danger of fighting alone?
But you ignored all that,
and now you're trying to take
revenge even if it kills you both!
Then, what am I supposed to do?
Don't fight when there's
absolutely no way you can win.
At the moment, we don't really
understand the nature of their stance.
So just retreat for now.
Avdol was cowardly stabbed from behind.
Are you saying I should run away?
Don't fight a battle that
may cost you your life.
That's what Avdol-san
was trying to tell you.
Hmm, just what the hell's all
that jabbering about you two?
I'm ready whenever you are, right?
Well, ready to lose?
Polnareff!
Don't let up, Zondai!
Get in vain!
Damn it.
All right.
I'm sorry, Polnareff.
Polnareff! Huh?
That guy, Avdol, died for you.
I guess you owe him one, right?
If you hadn't been here, he
wouldn't have died, right?
Damn, where's that bastard's main body?
Poledeth, just stay calm!
But you know what?
There's no need to be sad, Palmerev.
You'll see Avdol soon.
And your precious little sister as well.
What?
When you meet your little sister again,
why don't you ask her how I killed her?
Don't take the bait!
He's just trying to provoke you!
Bastard!
It's impossible for your
chariot to cut my hanged man.
I exist inside the mirror, where
your stand is unable to reach me.
Are you frustrated?
I'm sure.
Hey, whole horse, shoot him.
Let's finish off this idiot.
Yes, sirreeee!
Die!
Polnareff was shot by...
Emerald Splash!
To save Polnareff's life!
Damn, they're out of
the range of my stand.
Even if it hits the target, it's
too far away for maximum impact.
I guess Mr. J.
Giles hell-bent on ridding the
world of that Polnareff fella.
Hmm?
My apologies, Kakyoin.
If I could have avenged my sister's death,
I wouldn't have minded
being killed in the attempt.
But now I think I understand
what Avdol tried to tell me.
His sacrifice will not go to waste.
I will fight and survive.
So, Polnareff, do you
truly understand now? Yeah.
That's in lieu of
shaking hands to make up.
Now they're no longer just your enemy.
The next time they attack us?
You and I will bring them down!
That was close.
I'm at a fair disadvantage by myself.
I've never been one to
be the lone gunslinger.
Hell, there'll be another chance later on.
I'm sure I stabbed him with my sword.
But apparently I missed him.
I felt no resistance.
His stand, the Hanged Man, can launch
an attack from any reflective surface.
Even the smallest fragment will do.
The Hanged Man attacks my
reflection from inside the mirror.
But there's no way I can get myself
into something like a mirror.
How the hell am I supposed to
fight someone like him? Shit!
Palmadeth
You keep saying things like.
Inside the mirror.
Or the world of the mirror.
But there's no such world inside there.
What the hell are you saying.
You saw it too, didn't you.
He exists in the mirror.
But when you turn around, he's not there.
Yes, but a mirror is just
a reflection of light.
Nothing more to it than that.
Listen, I don't need you to tell me that.
Of course I know that.
I'm not talking about
common knowledge here!
If something like a stand can exist,
I'm telling you it's not so strange
that a world inside a mirror can exist!
Now what?
I suppose you still have some
sort of a problem with that?
No, but I do think the mystery of his
true nature is somehow related to that.
And somehow, his true nature
is also his greatest weakness.
Polareff!
He's in the chrome on the steering wheel!
What?
Kakyoin, you okay?
My chest really hurts, but I'll manage.
Get away from anything reflective.
That's it.
Now I get it.
Mirrors.
He followed us here from mirror to
mirror by a series of reflections.
Reflections, which means
it's actually light.
Its true nature is a stand of light.
Don't go near any reflective objects and
remove anything like that from your body,
too.
My brothers, it looks like
you had a car accident.
You must need medicine.
Buy from me.
I can give you a discount.
What?
Come on, buy it.
I'll make it cheap.
The bastard.
In a child's eye.
Hey, kid!
Don't look at us, you hear me?
Everything's fine.
See, there's nothing wrong with us, okay?
Now get away from here, you little brat!
You damn bastard!
Wait! Pull that F!
What will you do now?
You wouldn't poke this little boy's
eyes out with your sword, would you?
I've got you at last.
You can't escape now unless
you poke out this boy's eyes.
Poke out this boy's eyes, you say? Shit.
Stabbing Avdol-san from behind and
now using a child unforgivable.
Hey, Kakyoin.
In this situation, you don't
use a stock line like that.
Listen, when the time comes to take
revenge, this is the kind of line you use.
My name is Jean-Pierre Polnareff.
For all your crimes, for the
honor of my sister's spirit,
and so that my friend
Abdel may rest in peace.
Without fail, I will drive you
to the very depths of despair.
Forgive me, kid.
There, in Polnareff's eyes.
I'm not sure how it works, but he
can move at the speed of light.
Normally, it's a speed
beyond all recognition.
But if that kid's eyes were to close, I
knew his next move would be to my eyes.
And if you can predict that path...
Then cutting him with my sword is easy!
Over there!
Let's go, Kakyoin!
Ah! The medicine!
Let's go!
Let's go! Let's
go!
Bastard! Finally!
At last we meet, eh?
Mr. J. Guile.
Yes, I figured out your Stan's secret.
Frankly, your stand surprised me at first.
Although it was clearly visible, there
was nothing I could do to counter it.
But once I understood its true
nature, it was no big deal.
You can kiss your ass goodbye now!
So, allow me to finish you off slowly.
This is not Jake Isle!
Pull it off!
Shit!
Gee, Kyle, you're just a stupid
fool after all, eh, Boulder F?
You don't even know what I look like,
yet you carelessly approached,
thinking you'd won!
That guy's just a street peddler.
All I had to do was cut him with a knife
in the same place you injured the hangman.
Bastard!
Hold on now.
Take a good look around.
Hey, got around.
These travelers would like to
give all of you some money.
What's going on?
Do you realize what this means?
Ha ha!
You say you've figured out my stand?
You fool!
It's my stand, so naturally
I'm aware of its weakness.
Increasing the number of reflective
objects will make his path unpredictable,
and no longer will it be vulnerable.
Don't look!
Everyone, stop looking at us!
Now you can't escape,
or are you going to create an exit by
slaughtering the poor innocent peddlers, huh?
Polnareff, you sacrificed
your youth to pursue me.
Oh, how sad that you failed.
Oh, what a lonely,
wretched life you've led.
But don't worry, Polnareff.
After you leave this world,
I will live happily on in it.
Women at my feet,
catering to my every need.
Is it us they want to see?
Or that?
By the way, what an
entertaining little screamer!
Your sister was...
Bastard! Just wait!
I'm coming up there right now!
Polneneff, such words
are not appropriate here.
When the time comes to
take revenge you shouldn't
use words like bastard
you say it like this
My name is Noriyaki Kakyoin
so that my friend Abdo Sol and
the soul of my friend Alnaref's
sister will rest in peace
may Jay Gile atone for
these crimes with his life
I will give that gold coin
to whoever picks it up.
It's a gold coin, so shiny
you can see your face in it!
I got it!
I understand, Kakyoin!
Right there!
Chariot!
A-a
-a-a-a-a!
You are the one who's so
good at screaming, J. Guile.
I was wrong.
I'll do whatever you say,
so please forgive me.
My sister, my younger sister must
have said the same thing to you.
But you killed her anyway.
You killed her for your own sick pleasure.
How long have I waited for this moment?
From here, you'll be
screaming your way to hell.
But there are things I can't
leave to the demons down there.
Die!
Oh, my God.
A very fitting end for
someone named the Hanged Man.
This ain't no damn good for me.
I'm at a hell of a disadvantage alone.
Without a partner to back me up,
my gunfighting skills can't shine.
Better to be number two than number one.
That's my philosophy in life.
I best get on out of here now.
Bastard.
Jotaro! Joseph-san!
We already know all about Avdol.
Time was short, so we gave him
a simple but proper burial.
So, what should we do with this guy?
The bastard who stabbed Avdol-san
in the back was J. Guile.
But this guy is the one who
fired the bullet that killed him.
I see.
That settles it.
Let me be the one to carry out justice.
Spare me, partner.
I'll do anything you ask, okay?
Every one of them begging for their lives.
I'll teach you that you
can't get off so easy.
So, prepare to learn!
Please run, my dearest
hole horse. It's you.
Please, please run while I hold him.
You're my only reason for living.
Please escape while you can.
Who is this woman?
Thank you so much for saying that.
I gladly accept your offer and will
live on to see another sunrise. Bastard!
Dearest hole horse!
You know, I'm only running
away because I love you, honey.
Otherwise, we won't be able to go on
like this, loving each other forever.
See you, baby. Love you.
Wait!
Shit!
This woman! Stop it! Polnareff!
But that bastard killed Avdol
and she helped him get away!
We just can't afford to
go chasing after him now.
It's unfortunate, but we don't have
the time to make any side trips.
That's right.
In keeping with Avdol-san's intentions,
we need to put this matter aside for
now and continue with our journey.
All right!
Avdol.
May your soul rest in peace.
We will join you there soon enough.
Let's go, everyone.
Let's continue our journey to Egypt.
Look, Dio isn't going to be easy.
If the four of us want to beat this enemy,
we're going to have to stick together.
If any one of us gets out of line,
he's sure to take advantage of it.
Be careful.
How can he say something like that to us?
In his own way, he's dealing
with the trouble he's caused,
including the incident with Avdol.
Oh, what a pain.
Come on! Move it! Huh? Oh!
Avdol, you wait and see.
I promise I will avenge your death.
No, my son just died.
My dearest son, you perished.
Your body covered with horrible
wounds just like these.
Oh, you're agony.
I can feel it through the
pain of the astigmata.
God damn it, I'll fucking kill you.
I'll damn well make sure I
killed you with my own hands.
With my own stand.
Justice!
Oh, my God.